life is an exciting Journey filled with
possibilities and Milestones one of the
most important milestones in this
journey is retirement it's a new
beginning where we ReDiscover life and
pursue passions a phase of Life which we
all want to enjoy without any worries a
well-crafted financial plan can be your
compass to navigate towards a happy
retired
life introducing ICI Pro gold pension
savings a plan that serves as your
financial GPS for a secure and
worry-free retirement set your course
with flexible premium payment options
tailored to suit your needs choose your
investment period from 10 to 40 years
and watch as your path to retirement
becomes clearer with each step in your
journey with ICICI Pro gold pension
savings watch your savings grow from the
very first year with regular bonuses and
loyalty accumulations Paving your way to
a robust
future and when you arrive at the end of
your policy term you are in the driver's
seat you can withdraw a maximum of 60%
of your Corpus as per your convenience
in the form of a lumpsum and that do
taxfree and you need to purchase an
annuity plan with the remaining amount
what's more you can navigate life's
Milestones with confidence knowing you
can make special withdrawals for planned
and unplanned events without losing your
way you also get complimentary Health
checkups during your policy term with
ICICI Pro gold pension savings chart a
journey that's as rewarding as the
destination itself ICICI Pro gold
pension savings your retirement
[Music]
GPS